[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "But do you know where she was, for example, when James DiMaggio picked her up, or whether she went along with any part of this voluntarily?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "Well, I think she's got to be devastated as you expect.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 73, "question": "How do you describe her state of mind after all this?", "qSentId": 72}, {"answer": "Yes, we have a lot of interviews, we're still conducting, we're examining the evidence we seized from the fire here in Boulevard, as well as the crime scene investigations in Idaho.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "What can you tell me about how your inquiries have gone in that regard?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "You know, I was very relieved that Hannah was saved.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard how it all ended?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Yes, I can now confirm that, I wasn't able to talk about it before for obvious reasons.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Tell me about this?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "I can confirm that everything that's been reported by the woman who's been speaking out is absolutely accurate.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "And this incident with this 16-year-old girl the father had, what do you know about that?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "I'm positive that he had a suicidal plan.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "What -- do you think this is what is really behind all this?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "The parallels between my abduction and Hannah's abduction are the fact that we were both abducted by family friends.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "What kind of parallels did you see with this case and yours, and what advice would you give to Hannah Anderson about how you recover from it?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I think it all depends upon what your early childhood was like.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "And to hold down normal relationships, perhaps, with men as you get older?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "From the media reports that I read, it seems like the abductor said something to Hannah that showed that he was infatuated with her or was in love with her, in some sort of inappropriate way.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 179, "question": "What do you think should happen in that situation?", "qSentId": 178}, {"answer": "For me, I definitely think that I have moved toward almost a full recovery.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "What's the most effective thing you've been able to do for yourself, that's made you recover in that way?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "I think it's a combination of both.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "The more you've seen of this case, what do you think is the most likely motivation for -- a simple infatuation or a mixture of an infatuation coupled with all the trauma that James DiMaggio clearly endured at the hands of his own father?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "I mean, in a way, it's a classic abuser turned -- abused person turned abuser, isn't it?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "You know, it's -- in hindsight, it's -- you know, I keep looking back, and I've been thinking about it for the past five days, and it's still very much sort of a no.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "ORGAN: Did you at any stage see anything looking back from his behavior that could possibly have led you to think he might one day be this kind of violent or to kidnap somebody?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Absolutely, deception, lies, hurt.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "He must be wrestling with all this, wondering, how could this have happened?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "I think the bottom line is that she needs to heal, the way to heal is to start to go through the funeral or whatever services are going to be so those feelings can come out and then get into some good solid treatment.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "What did you make of what she said and what advice specifically for Hannah Anderson given the trauma, not just her own ordeal, but what she's now discovered about her mother and brother?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "I -- you know, apparently you never go out of therapy.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Are you back in therapy?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "No, he sure didn't seem happy to be there.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "And so (ph) my overriding question today (ph) is is he really going to stay in this race, or does the sense that you were getting from your encounter with him suggest that perhaps even he knows the game may be up?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Do you know what her role on -- in Hillary's 2016 campaign is going to be?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I'm not telling you.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "What will it be?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "I feel that what I've done has hurt her, yes.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "Do you feel like you've damaged her place in that world?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Well, my first take takeaway was just a clarity of the assumption from somebody who's, you know, one career (ph) move, one of the closest people to Hillary Clinton that she's running -- the unquestioned assumption that she's running.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 305, "question": "Was that your reading of that?", "qSentId": 304}, {"answer": "I don't have a good answer to that.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "The one question that actually I got most from like BuzzFeed staff and -- and the internet was -- was why not use Snapchat?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "I asked him that.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 358, "question": "Could he make another comeback?", "qSentId": 357}, {"answer": "Well, Ben, congratulations.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "...it felt like, you know, where are you?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I don't know why, but I -- what keeps coming through my head is something Al Pacino would say every time I try to get out, you pull me back in, Anthony Weiner, with this entirely ridiculous interview.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "Star, are you impressed by Anthony Weiner's latest fight-back interview?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "A lying and a laughing stock.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "...the (ph) sort of thing is it -- you know, it made him a bit of a laughing stock, didn't it?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "The biggest problem has been that Huma has always been the sort of stalwart second to Hillary without any question.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "But just broadly speaking, Star, on -- on the question of Hillary Clinton in 2016, can Huma stay as her right-hand woman, do you think, without damaging Hillary politically?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "And she's speaking to a constituency that she's going to need.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Is that your take?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I really -- well, from what I understand, and I'm only going to go on what I've actually heard on CNN right now is that the dog was on the helicopter or the -- with a bunch of staffs.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Do you share the outrage over Bo and his freebie?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "Well, it may be broken but it's still quite frankly the best system that they have across the world.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "What do we do about it?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "Now, all...", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "Is it -- is it, though?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "ONES: But three strikes you're out is supposed to be with good judgment.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 488, "question": "How can that be good justice?", "qSentId": 487}, {"answer": "Well, you know, what's -- what's interesting about this is I -- I'm of two minds.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "And should we start to forgive Paula Deen and allow her back into civilized society?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "I..", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "You know, I would actually probably agree with you on that.", "docId": "130812pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "...should we be slightly more forgiving, given she brought this out herself?", "qSentId": 526}]